Further, if we walk through the bottom of the building, we'll need to do that,
general questions to you.
Thank you very much.
I'd like to leave the streets to the light.
And I know that it's safe.
And we're going to have to put the distance.
On my nation, I don't know if you got any of this.
I don't know if you can adjust yourself.
Here's a gift, please.
Hey guys, I'm out there.
Everybody goes in and everyone's got the medio.
I'm pretty much proud of their own go-round.
Sure. I'm going to marry one of the city of상을.
My name is Pomerace and I'm from the City Manager.
And I'm a bit of the troll-down for about 20 days.
Why do you do this?
I have to apply an app and I need to do it hard.
John Bern, that's one of the most part of the mayor, Koleo.
I mean, the name is Martin, the director of the church.
Hi, Tom.
Two points.
What was the orange city clerk?
I'm going to jail.
I'm going to do it on there.
And drag it by me.
I'm going to try services.
I'm going to do it.
Four.
The special community events.
Traveling.
I brought everybody together.
The other is one of this problems.
They're going to do this.
About things that we need to bring them down.
My ideas which may have events.
Anything like that.
So we're going to open that up.
Just want to ask them.
Then we're going to talk about that.
On the bedside.
And these.
That's one of these we may have to share.
Maybe that does.
Talk to the bands.
I think she got this.
You know that list.
I don't know.
I don't care about anybody.
These are.
But this list with bands that are on the count.
This year.
We're going to be a coach.
She's got to get her on the count.
Is this on the bedside?
Yes.
We're going to talk.
This is on.
If you go to this at my end.
I'm going to pay that on.
They.
We've got in our calendar.
A lot of these.
We've just got in.
It's a funny last 24 to 48 hours.
And I said this is part of here.
I'm going to use up one again.
I'll mute that.
And within the terms.
part that we have a whole global distribution partners. And we've got email
on there, so we're constantly mailing out. And I was there. And hopefully
we'll open all of them. So if you grab a part free, go shoot me your email,
I'll ask you to do that. So we just put this out in the end.
Because we're getting ready to launch all of the first print experience
means that we do have a city for a marketing. And one of the biggest
ones is events. So if you go into the backing of all of our analytics
on the city side, we're going to post search for access.
People are searching for my own.
At the moment, it's thanks to you in my end of the moment.
Thanks to you in the moment. So this is a big part of what
drives people who can talk to the community of this.
And what drives people to our area outside of our local places,
it's a good sort of, I just had to say, well, let's put that on the agenda.
And this is kind of the pressure I didn't give it to most of the time.
I mean, this is what they didn't think.
And we added that all the way to try and have all the way to try and have all this morning.
This book of those events that they've confirmed now.
So this kind of gives you guys a kind of idea of what we know is on the calendar.
And there's probably a lot that people have to go to chat.
And one says both, and they find a lot of it.
This is like a work of document that we need to add things to.
If I don't know why I'm going to go to the end of this,
I'm going to go to the end of this.
This is where there's an issue.
I'm asking you what the challenge is.
So that one.
Why not?
That's actually a new day.
She was supposed to be here by her member.
And she asked her what the first few push players.
She's wearing actually damn in time at today.
More people are just going to put in.
She's the manager of the conference.
If he feels really good about it, take a self for that.
And pretty strong.
And honestly, it's not a law of law of law.
It's not a law of law of law.
We'll take a soul.
It's about a town of code.
And then more.
Nothing huge.
I mean, you can't talk about community events a little bit.
That's a huge risk.
It's kind of the moment that it's a high price.
But it's something different.
It's something I think that.
And then you show it a chance to.
Trying to do something different.
It has a target.
Because a lot of people have to see how people respond.
We have to show you there.
This is a, you know, it's a thing so social distancing.
You know it will be okay.
If you're going to be able to let us, or maybe it will get to that.
By the way, people will be okay.
How are you?
Sure.
Some kind of thing.
Oh, the box thing.
Yep.
This will be exciting.
So, especially if you want to go.
Okay, now we have to go to the Chancellor of that list.
What kind of things?
Actually, it's not a business to the dear.
I'm sure you got that some.
I have one.
That's a business.
I don't know if you guys ever go to the J-Carshow.
But I mean, we go over here.
My family goes to different people from now.
There are people there from Florida.
I mean, it is a huge event and they make a lot of money.
So, what makes that event more special than the other cost?
And because so many people bring their cars from so many different towns.
And they do it.
Because they let them give their names on the industry.
Which I know.
And cause an issue.
But they have at least like it everywhere.
It's very.
Watched.
But I want to be on the other hand.
And a lot of the towns don't allow that.
So that's why people come to change because the town.
Utilizes that.
That's what people want to do.
They want to show off their cars.
And I think that's a big.
I think that's a big deal.
And I'm not willing.
Used to do it.
But.
And it hasn't a few years.
And we still got to go.
They might want to see what they want to do.
That's the big thing.
I think.
I mean.
I remember a lot of the thing.
She sent down to the day as Garcio.
They allowed them to do our house.
On one of the local streets.
And I know that's probably what brings them a lot.
People have to sign up and they can see like 20.
Right.
We have to have.
And there is something that can take these.
And as far as.
I said that many all of them just have to be a sub-operated, simply for that.
That's the biggest.
Yeah, I think it's on them.
I know why.
I think my client is, there's started to talk about treasuring, can they?
Yes.
So I think I just did a start from attending meetings and to be for that.
And I don't know why.
I can help a sub-operated couple of treasuring.
But actually, very, very important.
And I was, so there is a talk from planning for a treasuring angle.
They have treasuring.
I mean, they have treasuring.
You know, the guy, you like the movie, I don't know about it.
They have the movie.
Yes.
The local businesses that have 118 stands.
There's kids from 118 stands.
The schools came in and they were selling hot dogs and hamburgers to raise money for the schools.
And they're so much getting a look on it and helping them to come in and sell.
And then they, a lot of side of all people do that, so they bought the crap out of the
women.
And then went to the elementary schools, whatever they wanted to do, different,
and other things.
But the difference is that we're going to be the random things that students do,
and they're not going to have to form them.
They don't have names for you doing that or, and we're going to set up to say,
what people are going to run to do, and we can prepare for that.
So a little bit of the importance is to stuff like that.
And they don't want to keep us from doing that.
I would just encourage that, just do it that they're a stop car.
Well, they don't want to put out their names.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Now we're going to run.
Okay.
I mean, I don't know how we're going to figure it out.
I mean, to have a car that was here.
And we did it in cooperation with the main,
the main street was active.
Something else.
We did it.
I would have never been the moment.
I don't really know.
I don't know.
We have to point out this.
This is what they've very, I don't really know why.
It is, it's like placing the same.
You've got to have stuff.
And something like that.
And you know, historically, bring your cars out,
etc.
And talk to that car.
It's just pretty boring.
That's like the way to like it was.
Much of our, like, safe of long turns,
decided to look at it.
They will,
Jay, you get to drive your car.
You get put in context on this looking car.
Loud is car.
Jack is car.
I mean, there's, there's so many different competitions
just people can enter in.
And it's just different from any other car.
So it's quite an event.
Even Buffalo runs.
But what runs you just sat up there and looked at it.
But the number on it, you know.
When these people can actually do something with their car.
But they've looked thousands and thousands of dollars.
Dollars in.
It makes a difference.
I think the past two years, I think that's been a day.
I mean, you can go.
I think it's been pretty good.
I mean, she didn't know who was, and she didn't know who was.
He wants to have some things to do there.
You know, we tried to do the cruise.
The first year we did the one.
And he's kind of getting a friend.
He's just, he just tricks on the work.
I think there's, I think the burnout deal is to,
the need to use to do that, I don't know.
Please don't do this.
And then there's a car.
It was pretty good.
It's a cruise.
I think there's one block.
And right there in front of us.
The shallow side.
You can go.
I've got mixed feelings on this.
Mr. McKinney, can't hold failures if you go wrong, but I think if you're a person that is in one area and I think even if you need a group that's crazy, I think that there are police cruisers next day with that
Mr. McKinney, you know, so group that's crazy.
And I have to say what the person is, of course, said he had a liability in terms of concerns for a while now, and I've got to put a picture on this.
See what the liability is doing to be done, but I think we can move a little point.
I can't close.
The adoption is, well, actually, it's bounding on that's a great thing.
Things like most part, it's got numbers in the outside of the room.
I love the image part, so I have a lot of time, but most people don't have it.
Having some time to do a lateral event with that, I think it is to work with something that's going to be found on what makes it unique.
One of the things that I talked to the whole guys about doing,
I was like, I showed a little one with like a part that you could go off.
We're doing, we're doing a little street meeting.
It was kind of sketching a couple of guys that asked about doing like home grooves,
like maybe you won't live in a competition with a part that's lost in fear or whatever.
And then, let me remind you that there's a fertilizer.
First off, you know, he's like, that's a love that name.
You can actually talk about personal life.
Sponsoring it, which was really cool.
We kind of have all of the elements, like, you know, as a piece of sponsors.
And I think we're made really well.
Some sort of like that with a workshop.
There's one of the things that I've noticed is I've moved in.
There's a lot of a little bit of amazing smokers around here.
It's like, you know, it's kind of, it makes parts of you that I've moved in.
Very unique, I've never had it.
And a lot I got to think that we need a way to kind of expand our own to the local talent.
The way that it looked, yeah.
Thank you.
Do you live in basketball, but then on?
Yeah.
I've got to go to basketball team.
But that was a little bit of a problem.
Probably that I have to share.
local, anybody who has a motor or a thermonars, anybody who needs a turning thing, or
even just a regular system, so I can, to dollar fly in or whatever you have.
When we talk all of our grew up in the middle of the festival, every weekend, in one season of stuff
in the most successful, we go in our roots like red or festival, my hometown, hometown is a bunch
of the release of cities. We just found it on that and made it the end of it.
People show that thousands of people go to a thermonars, because I think if you go through
the work, you can try to do anything. I think there's a very long queue, so people are
having to really tell you that there's some great birds chasing the ice ground, and you can
prefer some amazing years. There are some of them that's been as far as stuff, so you're out here.
I've been on the ground where the birds are using an extra, which I don't know, I mean, those
really do work at my most found on that. I mean, why do we need to make it completely hours?
One thing I had thought about, it was that I thought God was saying with our roots,
there's a Springville festival, or one of them, volunteers, that you catch them, then we have,
like you guys are out there, the guy, and we're going to live them off, do it with that.
And if you go from there, like that's right, those guys might have to do it themselves.
I thought they might have a little bit, but that's a little bit of a festival.
You know, you got guys coming in from all of the other states, because they share the problem with that.
It's fine to the right part of the year to do it when you have enough space to leave people.
You see how the places have strong areas, those festivals,
Jeff, there's Jeff a little bit of festival festival, yeah, I mean, I would see it in just like a grant,
if you were there a grant a lot of things, you could remember and then I have to be with all these
special things, you know, for the people who bring their lives in.
It's really pretty up there.
So the yard has it set up.
Yeah, it's okay.
It might come in, I mean, you may have been,
because I do some support on the side.
You have, like, the state come to everyone
come all and do it, as much as it'll have been.
So you're saying, bring my head in, and the change in shape
or something there.
Because I've got to tell you a little bit about it.
I think their concern is, is I, you know,
you had these high-dollar dogs, and we did do this.
I asked him about the kind of disease on the down.
He said, well, that worrying would be,
he didn't have his high-dollar dog, and he,
you know, they pull it up, the fancy trade
that's a little bit of an engineering thing
for what you work in terms of trade that puts your dog in.
For those of the ones that you see on my DSP in,
the dog run, yeah, you know,
those of them that don't jump across.
That's what they do.
They didn't have enough of it.
They were like, you know, the dog would go,
I have my out there, and they treat it up,
and then buy it, and they catch me going,
it looks so bad, you know.
So I'll work at it somewhere.
And you can take you out there.
That's it.
It's a struggle this year.
It's a code in the blood, but then also, you know,
the casinos are not doing the wrong sorts of events
that we've been accustomed to them doing.
For a long time, we get a lot of over the blood
of those cancers.
You know, they're coming in and eating our restaurants.
They're here at the bar in two days.
We're not.
That's all we're going to wait and I think it'll come back
if you think, kind of, I'll get back.
You know, because we're kind of eating the dinner,
but we're seeing a huge hit in our intelligence
straight here in town, where there's a lot of problems
around the time and it's in its headquarters.
And they are struggle for them.
And I think they think, first of all, it goes through.
We can come together, and my client is,
you know, this is going to be my 15th child
with me going to plan that.
And there's saying that I wish you could do a lot of this.
Sometimes comes down to the budget capacity.
And you know, with choosing, do we go after one
and really, really big to men?
You know, that idea, get one out of this group
that we say, this should be our, like, consciousness,
where you need, you know, you said,
and kind of a general little bit to think about
if you try to go after one, really, really big thing,
or if you try to spread it out over, you know, six or seven months,
of, you know, unless we're going to talk to a lady about ideas,
you know, one time, a month is the first time.
You know, it was the first, when Jean and then used to do it,
we marketed it, or it was all the support Saturday and a month.
And every once that month, a month, a month, a month,
a month, a month, a month, a month, a month, a month, a month.
I think that's all we've got to think about is, you know, who's going to respond to it?
You know, there's some events we do, the chamber doesn't live in, that's really take care of what we call our old apartment.
We're thinking that we said it on a brainstorm about it and think it was going to come in and start to tell her.
You know, what's big enough is that she's going to be able to have a date where it's over the weekend, that she would not have had and they would have been empty.
And those are the kind of things, like if you could be saying, you should guys think maybe, maybe not to buy it, but when we were here,
you know, what are some of those things that we can do? We are in a huge impact in our Contella right now.
We normally all be there at the 3 million in receipt, put the dollars, the Chinese dollar properties in a calendar year, and 2020 towards 2.8 million.
It's one of the lowest years that we have in a very, very long time to find out our Contella's really willing to go in that right now.
So, just something else that kind of adds to the discussion that's when you're thinking about what is that or the unity?
Something that we do that's one really, really big in it, or that's something that we kind of do that's multiple things throughout the month that really try to help get people on our hotels and look at our restaurants and spending money in our art.
But I do because the city is art, look at the $1.00. I'm trying to figure out, you know, if you guys all are spending at our local stores and the local dollars are all turning over, but my job, I'm just thinking, how do I work in the new dollars from that side of my hand?
So that you guys aren't happy to do the ones that support Walmart and Wolverine in all the time. How do we get those people that are passing through here? How do we get them to slot here and how do we gain some of those new dollars?
And I'm just telling you guys who've been to the art, and I would like to have them on here because it's really, is the driver for us, our Contella.
And I know that they better once we go to the other side of COVID, and I just think that 20, 22, we'll be back to the private event, but let's get to that point.
We've got a lot of reasons to go to that point. I love to talk about seeing how to gain something within the order where do you go to see if you can kind of gain as well?
That's the, you know, down the road that's completely made to be within the time you can type to the museum and have a little bit of the right.
There you go.
It's saying those people are soft, you know?
Before you turn away, we don't realize that we're a remarkable art thing.
Maybe we're the poor, which a lot.
You see, many people can kind of end there.
There's so much right there.
They're beautiful.
Things with families.
Or, you know, if we did have some kind of people,
they're a whole bunch.
It seems like a good space to possibly do something special.
Okay.
Well, but that, you know,
and that would probably be the kind of you guys who wanted to do.
So I have an idea.
So I helped, kind of,
Chris, to me, Smith, run day.
It's almost, it does back into a partial list for kids.
We did a power bills meet in on-way straight commerce.
And we had like four or five food trucks show up.
And there were people that came in to local and city.
And I'm telling you what, these people stood up these little power wells.
They were going to 40 miles per hour.
It was insane.
And these kids had a blast.
We, you know, it would bring food trucks in.
They'd have to bother local residents or whatever.
They'd come in.
These parents.
I mean, I've been seeing dad so mad.
In my life, they're kids not when he needs power well-being.
But it was a blast that didn't call it doesn't cost hardly any money.
I mean, you probably would have to have some city officials or whatever.
You know, please, there.
But you brought in a little town of commerce.
My goodness.
They got in.
200.
We had eight entries of kids.
And there was a blast.
The kids loved it.
Parents were, parents were involved.
And it wouldn't take a lot.
I mean, you can have one of those little roads over there at the review.
I mean, there's a lot in love.
Down you go.
And they didn't know.
Yet, well, people that put in a pot for like ten dollars.
They were representing the orders and these kids were money.
And it would bring nobody around here.
We need to utilize them for the biggest town.
But then 25 miles.
Drop one row.
And then they did some amount.
So if it costs a lot of money, the amount of payers and all of a sudden,
you want it.
There's nothing to do with kids here.
Nothing.
There was something about there that we had to do.
Like if we had to have seven or four kids, more even not just necessarily kids,
even adults, all of all, or shoes, stuff that would be difficult to set up.
That would be the other things to do with society.
So what are the things that the mayor and that would,
some folks about this week was our primary part.
The place is point to be such a large township,
regionally, we are part of the market as much more.
Because you can go to the home, go to your health, be straight.
They normally don't own Thursday nights for the seven.
During the season.
But one of the things we talked about is how do we use that as a platform.
Right?
That the event is really just a platform for what else can we do with?
We do with it.
But how do we create more of a draw with cook-offs and children who have been bringing in other
opportunities for retailers, for food trucks, or any of things we could do that would
help those of the economy, or to talk about, you know, love, love, love, love, that is the
core title of love, love, love, love, love is getting together with our part of the market
and using that to expand on it and try to find the new space for it in town, and learn
with the cloud for more events and spider space, maybe having an opportunity for covered
periods. So it was less acceptable, whether, but that's something I think, I really like
everybody to think about is, what could we do with that as a platform that Expand
wanted to create a draw and, honestly, the fact that we're doing it on 39,
technology, we're not competing well, we're doing it. If we're on 39, because
the other barge has been region, we're taking priority from us on that matter, so that's
already from us on that side anyway. You need to flip that. You need to become the largest
in the region. So the people choose to come here and use that time slot so that we can
grow and expand it out of that product location and product spots. I think there's an
untapped and reasonable issue. We know what it's like. One of the things that I think, if you look
with the holidays and each small town that has kind of exploded, it's found their thing.
That's because the tourism and the availability of the town, almost every single small town
that I can think of that has done that. So I was pre-part and saw a telephone. I didn't even take
the program area. Again, I've heard about the program area. They all have one central gathering place
that they started with. Now I'll start with the more integrated town town. So I was pre-part
with the tourism area. I'd love to be able to actually go back to here. All of those things
circulating on the spot, and then they grew up from there. I'm not saying that you can't have a fence
in the park, because I agree that the tourism is just massively going to be utilized. A lot of times that's
the easiest thing is because you don't know what the weather is going to do. You don't know what the
river looks like. They can start anyone in the poor area that becomes your gathering place for your town.
Whether it's the park park, the Coleman area, right there. I believe that those as your events begin to grow
out of that area, that's a centralized focus. People begin to identify like this. You picture the whole
of this, you picture the first national language, the free all the buildings down down there.
They start to identify my handle with those opinions, you know, you may go in the words,
they were back in for the first part of the youthful part down, it tends to grow here because they focus on one small area,
they're just focused on one identity, and then it's an experimental American, and they've got to grow up all over their town.
I think if we can concentrate on, just the particular part down, but starting in one place that identifies us,
that we have one gathering place, I think it will grow out on the map, you know, I think that's one of those,
and I would like to tell the whole thing is that I will do that.
That was part of the part of my mission.
I don't know if the word like this.
We started with the word that we did at the downtown, just called the entertainment district,
there was no entertainment here, but eventually we would see more parts of our restaurants,
we would be through the more of all that stuff we came together there, and now that we're in,
there's even a district is a walk-able, I think it's on the south side,
but it was from that utilization of people who start right here, it was a book, it was a letter,
I think that's a thing, instead of shotguning all over the place sometimes,
I think you'd have to kind of put this down on one thing, and go over there.
And that's just good.
That made me think of it because I've heard of it sometimes, because it's a good one, it's not good,
but it does play second, it'll pull out a lot of the reasons,
and maybe that needs to be the sort of point to know that part down.
I doubt what I hear that is, but the downtown, that's all the more people in the downtown,
and hopefully the best thing for downtown.
And it like this car show, I mean, if we have cars on that on both sides of my extreme,
then if you drop down the middle, if you drop down the middle, if you drop down the middle,
if you drop down the middle, if you drop down the middle, if you drop down the back,
you drop down the front, if you drop down the main street,
if you see all the cars, you have different areas set up the food,
if you're getting into whatever kind of thing.
I was going to grab some stuff down there, and I'm going to take a car show,
to do a battle of competition, along with the car show,
that brings that up, and there's kids, something to do together.
It's playing well.
All the time, all the time, all the time, we want that battle of competition.
So we're going to go on all the competition, so the people of the there,
and part of the people of the bottom, put all the left together,
and you got one echo in the middle, right there.
In the middle, but the car, or the worst kids to be,
or you can have to learn how something like somewhere.
But I think that I don't dare to make it for a decent man,
but they don't have something for everyone in the family.
I worked at REC and they always talk about the things that's only like the main part of what it does.
Business doubt is something that actually gives you things that's something that's like that.
Can you have a little of any of you want to see the rest of the space?
Can we have the partners?
The partners don't have the truth.
Yeah.
Do you want to see the other thing?
The partners don't have the space.
Bring them to a bowl of that stuff.
What's your name?
It's just a metaphor.
They'll do it.
They're all talking about that.
You know, we five, I don't remember how long ago was that we were done.
We used to do all the chlorine and part of it.
Just to kind of people walk in all the time and wish me to have this.
We did it.
And then one year, the Jordan boy did a good work of treating it up to the same time.
And brought out a lot of it.
It's part of it.
We're talking here and down.
And so after that, like I said, we're not going to work on it.
We're talking for your time.
And then it's like we need, kind of on the same thing.
Like that needs to transition and do a huge amount of things.
You know, when people look back, people think that's when they would schedule their reunion.
We're a lot for the union.
So it needs to be on the calendar of staying there every year, every year.
This is the weekend for my activities.
You know, on the spoon dough festival, if you did that, that's going to be probably too early in the year.
It's going to be a bit more important.
But you wouldn't have to settle in the car.
So it's going to be a bit more important.
So there's two things you can have to get on the table.
Both for the union management, they've got to close together.
It'll go off.
The other place to plan it.
I think it will.
Why do you have to plan it?
But you have it.
No, it's good.
I mean, I've got a lot of the same list you have.
I think it's fantastic list.
The idea is that the concepts you want to talk about.
Of course, Charles, let's talk about mainstream.
You know, I can't help but go back to the way it used to be.
It wouldn't be right.
We'd have a big sidewalk cell.
It's the best way to admit it.
That's what I remember.
We've got to go downtown and be able to walk around the street.
I'm cool.
I thought it was kids.
But they had a blocked off.
And you just have four access to it.
I think it has.
I think it won't be that.
It's a big thing.
And it's really fantastic, I think, just getting the draw
and taking advantage of all the work, right?
Strings the life post, things, we got to get people exposed
to start creating the memories in, and then.
How do you want to partner with it?
I want to start on another boxing match.
So I'd love to find the five of us.
We listened to it really well.
My problem with this, I couldn't even make a straight thing
after I got to the stage.
We will this day, we can fly this day, right?
I'm asking you, how many times do you want to make the show?
Really, you're the only other thing.
You've been here for a long time.
No, I was trying to get a full drum drum for you.
You're beautiful.
All right.
That's pretty good, isn't it?
And then, kind of what I want to know about this was for us to kind of pick something and really work towards making that.
And to me, kind of looks like the things we've talked about, these are five years, four of them together.
And I can really do it with me. And if I saw it, I'll leave you.
So I'm sort of first here as a part of this successful, because if we keep thought away, I have a nature like a better act.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you very much.
And we'd like to do it a bit.
That people look forward to doing it.
I think we have a lot of different kinds of people who are sick and tired of staying home.
I think I think that person who might remember us in it.
Yeah.
I mean, I think this is something we can possibly pull off this year.
Is this something?
I don't know.
So now we have to stand in the manner for...
Oh my god.
That's what we do.
I don't know.
I mean, if you're already at your own goal.
You know.
I have two racers.
So we go down below the name of the racer.
But you know, there'll be five thousand people out there.
And that brings people five people.
I do.
Like I said, like that.
I think sometimes, you know, they, it's underutilized.
I think we can figure out why we're going to start a very big park.
And then you know, drive on to your age.
And all the way.
I don't think they're going to be there.
They don't have to be there.
I think they have to.
I think we will be there.
So you know, maybe that's why they're going to be there.
And they don't have to be there.
And you just come back and you know where we are.
You know.
People don't tend to be there.
They don't have to be there.
No matter what we do, just come to the polls, we're doing the right thing.
And I'll just come back and we can.
And we have to be there.
And we can.
Yeah, we can.
I'm going to try to do it.
to, they're, they're, you know, they're getting a retribution weekend with their kids.
But they're going to take their kids and the dogs or whatever.
And also the gas station goes against wrong.
Some crackers, then they are not at all at what you can.
What you can do.
Thank you.
That would be a bowl of, if that's, if that's a strength to weigh, but
I'm sure you'd present it to the people.
You can't, can't.
It's a very...
I guess I'm focused on this,
but I got a lot of that little bit of a little bit of a little off of you.
Just got to think about that car show,
I'm going to zip up and go over to Rennie.
My idea is to just, like, outside of all the things they need.
I'm just a little bit to back to that,
make a little better, make a little shot on here,
make a little more attractive.
But I love a fact that if you do car show,
you can power those, lift it,
because that brings that in something else.
To do something together.
I don't know.
I think you always have,
and some bubbles in the right direction,
but I don't know what to do.
Well, and all the amount you do,
if you've got to make that base,
probably starting in a lot of here.
It's kind of in a lot rather than,
you can do it from that base.
You've got a car to go to the open for more of those,
though, that's what we can do.
And, I guess, I guess, the key is,
that everybody is at the bar down, so now,
you know,
around competition,
there are no, you know,
keep the discipline,
maybe,
you'll keep talking about,
over the few cars,
and, you know,
probably,
for two or three years of liability,
that, you know,
you can probably set up some barriers,
something down there,
where you can,
you can have some spectators,
and there's something,
when you're all,
they can just go up down through a deal,
either.
I don't know,
like, what's that?
I don't know.
You can reach out to the city manager,
something for days,
like, how they do it,
and what do they do?
I mean,
I don't know,
they can have a group.
People try it,
so,
people wanted to realize
the mainstream,
you can do a mainstream.
So,
it's,
what do they have?
I don't know.
Gosh,
we've been with a bit,
I don't know.
That's 10 years,
and we're,
oh, I know,
it was really hot.
I think you know,
they do it,
they also have a,
like,
a couple of times,
five or four times.
I know,
like,
four or six times in a short time,
five or four times in a short time,
four times.
So,
we can go into a,
and,
for a long time.
So that's 10,
so it's there.
but then,
like,
I'm just going,
okay,
and,
I'm just going,
so that's it.
So,
we're going to,
and just be like,
And so choose pretty, I mean, counterwise can you think about filling in empty areas, really probably to lie.
Yeah, like the last weekend in the lie.
The audience, we're there.
Yeah.
And then that way, that kind of spread it out.
It gives businesses an opportunity where we don't have everybody in town to say,
we can, we try to spread it out a moment.
But you guys, you have good weekend, never weekend.
Looks like you'd have to use those very first week or two.
When you join?
Oh, very first.
I just think that at the end of the talk.
Yeah.
Did you say there was an office?
Okay, they didn't.
They didn't.
But, I mean, people spend money on their cars.
They're going to, they want to show it.
They didn't.
They've got a couple of questions.
I'm sorry.
They've got a week in, maybe, even between.
You know, I think they're like the future.
They're like, don't.
If you look at it, you lie.
We've got, uh, or those are, uh,
Stay, they'll talk about the second week in the lie, which will be,
You know, a lot of people may pay attention to the lie, but when you get close traffic to the end of the month,
and if you have an after and a time that it, a lot of people that,
That's a nice one to explain to you.
So, last week, August, August, August, September, September, and September.
And you're going to run into football.
You're going to run into them.
You're going to get them.
All in full area in the front.
The solution for me to do.
I think something.
And I have some, I guess, something about how we can make this car show fabulous.
That's pretty good.
But, for the puppies, one of the puppies you're in between now, and that's not the lead.
Okay.
You have a suggestion.
You have a suggestion on this.
Come out.
All right.
We're going to run five.
And, specifically, we have those big business opportunities.
But, you know, the one that's staying in there, then you want to get a line up.
Or, you think, like that.
Did you have a phone call that I'm doing?
You talked to me a few days ago.
It's about that.
You know, that video place is close.
I want to open it.
I don't know if all of it is wanted.
members of the family.
I don't know.
What's there?
A lot.
They want me to say.
They said it might split into two businesses.
Two properties.
They said, well, I'm not.
Yeah.
But we should not hear more.
We should not hear more.
We'll go back to what?
We need to talk to him probably.
He's looking about the end of the family.
We'll go back up right now.
You know what?
Let's go.
They'll be.
Well, there's one more to dice.
They want to cross.
They don't know.
Great.
And right now.
They don't know.
They're trying to finish the store and cartage.
And so they get done.
One cartage.
They need to go up here.
So.
That's that.
They don't.
The family is.
They don't know.
Whether or not.
They don't.
So, they don't anymore.
They don't know.
They don't.
They're not.
They thin.
They make a lot bigger part.
And folks don't.
They make stores here.
Yeah.
They have aTom deficiency.
So pop like that in the suit.
Yeah.
And, you know, they pop like that.
oped, quoted only.
You know.
And all.
We don't want to.
six preparation, a presentation of the question was on,
you'd tell him, Dillon, and Henry, who's the dog.
Excuse me, just to want to know what I supplied to you.
Yep.
Okay.
The two things that I supplied to them,
the Denver said, later the buildings have been turned.
The five standing was, they paid every study done,
and the sprites, ready to.
contact us around the areas to which I think there was like a lot of this that they charged
tenors that and played these. And whenever I reached out to them, almost all of them said
that we don't even have electricity, that's how it's forced to somebody else. Obviously, it has
the bulk of any electricity for this and a year. So I was kind of trying to get them to consider
or photographing that percentage back to something normal. And I'm going to write all of my
my kids through. I'm going to be as though animals would be the hand for electricity
once. They're like, he was 1.5. He had to release it on. So the advice was to find
buyers that buy them and all of these, he's in one of the household. Why are we so high? What's
really local? The ones that were 10% were like, either way bigger than that or a fractional
or a size even. I mean, it just wasn't, it didn't seem consistent to me. It was a race
that they used to be in after the information. I hope you could see a pretty much what
I think is kind of grabbing you, you know, so I think we should look into the view of something
about that. Obviously, when we have the excuse that the high utility bills and possible under
rooms and a lot of people talk about that, and it's nice people to be in the terminal and that
back now. If you were usually up to eight other ones, there are extra things that's almost in
some countries. But then that can be looked into, and maybe something on that one, that
would not have the boundaries like that. And then the other one is the five other people,
not having your bill. I would just always pull to be a money. When I got into it, I came in
and came up with it one day. I watched the guy in front of me, he goes, here it is past you. He's
still left, you know, he's got a cash in there. He goes, here it is, he has two, he's going to
come on. He did that, he was a bill, and because he didn't know it was a bill, he couldn't
know it was a bill. I was like, what are we trying to do here about that? I dressed at the
very little, which 20 seconds a moment, and I was over the phone. So I just don't understand it.
They're like, we're going to charge for not having your bill. The other thing is to make it something
more reasonable. We're just doing that. Those are things I've brought about more of the
working at again, because they just seem like a poor business. Any other, so in Josh and I
have talked about this, I know he's brought up, so we thought this would be the best place for this
kind of to come up for this committee and talk about this since there's a lot there that I learned a
little bit from the staff. I think there's more information that we want to present to this group.
And kind of walk through this, it's all because these are things that if they mean a lot to you all,
they think these are areas that we're concerned, there are something we'll be looking at. Then we
have to put this on the table for a second. So obviously tonight we've already had a pretty good agenda.
So I think Josh brought some great things up at the next meeting, we'll come and kind of
resend the mechanics behind these first questions.
So we could kind of all understand the barriers or the challenges that are there.
And then, you know, what are the options that we have?
This is the city.
I'd love to hear a really your thoughts on the options that we have.
What do you think is appropriate?
You know, should we be changing these things?
Is there an impact somewhere else financially?
Is it more important that we reduce the 10% and maybe have a shift of revenue in one area?
So we'll come prepared to do that on our next meeting and that might consume most of our next meeting
and maybe talk about that.
That's really the 10% late fee for the, you know, the 10% late fee.
The final fee.
I think we're more prepared to talk about another trip.
I'll turn that over and then talk a little bit about what we've prepared and kind of know where
we're at because I think we've already got traction in that.
So there's something that the administrative staff I've been working on.
We've been going through all the policies and we've been telepathy department for many, many months.
That's a very tedious process for instance on just this, this one on the $5 fee.
We probably had seven meetings trying to go through the reporting as existed.
Why was that this way?
What can we do to better?
So for instance on that one, just one of the illustrations was somebody thinking,
they're on multiple accounts.
And I mean, you know, that occurs.
We're buying this.
That's, we could figure out from what information they were doing this.
And it ended up with some other, you know, that they wanted to reply to you being shot off.
I'm going to please look forward to seeing that by a freezer and all of me because we didn't apply it the way they wanted it.
Although they didn't tell us how they'd want it.
And so I'd hosted the kinds of stories to act.
Now, as I'm understanding it, this particular fee was put in about $1,000 a year.
It was recommended to us at least.
I'm just saying great study is the life fee.
Of course I wasn't here then.
I don't know if anybody is doing this right now is here at that time.
But in assessing what we're trying to accomplish.
with this D is to accurately obtain us to where there's supposed to go to.
And if a person brings in their bill or other, there's so little ways that I didn't
apply, which has a supposed to go to.
And if I identify it, that's right.
You know, exactly where there's supposed to be a client, but the problem is that a lot of people
know, they definitely know that much.
Well, the way we work, our way to be the process, if somebody's having in, they have one
of people out, only one of them out.
You know, it should be a problem to figure out one of them that she got in.
So that's one of the first things that we did in this process is saying, well, there's no point
in having that fee, if we're only going to be applying it to one of them, they can't
possibly figure that out.
Generally, if you add to their customers, maybe you'll stand, then they get to be a little more
complicated.
Always go to their addresses and other things to figure out where that's supposed to go without
a regular difficulty.
So one of the very first decisions that we made in this process is there really isn't a reason
to have that fee or somebody that's paying online.
That was a simple fix.
So then, is there a reason for it if there's somebody's name on multiple things?
So we had, for instance, in the old college, there's 15 or 20 or 30 different accounts there.
And then, often, to this check, with no statements, we can't figure out, not think
that we can add up on what their different bills are, amounts to the amount of the check
that they're using.
And so, you know, it's just a huge problem trying to properly allocate the money for it, where
they wanted to go.
And there are other examples.
So, as we told, of all of those different meetings, we have come up with the proposed section
2438, the amendment, this section 2438, like I said, it's a good product that several meetings
for several months, a month, we have, I think it's pretty self-explanatory at this point.
But if anybody has any questions on it, you're the first one who's outside of the administrative committee to seek this.
Somebody who wants some significant issues or problems with this are intent.
This point is to be presenting this to the council for the next year.
We play them.
We work out the problems where it's fair and it's reasonable.
And a change is the goal that we're trying to achieve.
We're trying to achieve this with an accurate allocation of payments to people like.
If anybody sees the problems, I would like to ask you.
We'll do the question I have as a sense here in the five dollar administrative fee will not be applied in the following situations.
Let's receive the drop box.
Okay, so if I come in and I'm in my restaurant, my home and check with no count number, no bills, no address, why am I not being charged by dollar fee?
No, I'm not going to get a couple more on the stage than you by dollar fee.
But if I come in I'll be charged by dollar fee.
Okay, when somebody comes in, who it simplifies and hopefully it simplifies and press because we can ask this question.
Which answer is your comment?
When it's life in the drop box, when it's meal, we don't get that opportunity until we have to refresh my memory of why we made that decision to modify five dollar fee in those instances.
If I come in, I'll be charged by dollar fee.
No, I can't remember that.
Yeah, we did that.
At that point, but I can't think of the deal.
There's a lot of money coming in that morning.
It happens to be a shut off morning.
I mean, there's just no time.
Well, we've done the way to play here.
Well, there would be time because we'd run the list at night and there's no way we could process all those bills.
You know, shut up there.
We get this many bills in the drop box.
And there's just no way to get all that process in time.
I may be too.
She doesn't.
I don't want Jack both.
When I'm never gone, you're not going to go to the front out.
You're not going to go to the front out.
I assume that this is a lack of a lot of issues with the genesis of the little problem, right?
That is a part of it.
Yes.
So it wouldn't be simple to, I mean, I don't know, to be automated or to some of the genesis of the liability,
that you're not holding a city accountable.
This is the property you want to pay to work.
It's a liability issue that a customer assigns off on that.
I would point that the inventory is the city room.
I would point it to be the first item off.
I wanted to go to one more main street.
And it would never add a lot more time into the whole process.
That is the other thing that we are trying to eat with the time frame.
I would pour the customer down as well as where our CSR is.
Right now we don't even have a sign online.
They just have a sign for that.
That is, that makes it quicker and easier for the money.
I mean, there should be an incentive for people who have a lot of money.
Great incentive.
Right incentive.
Just like people who have like, I get, like, in my apartment.
I set up a lot of there.
I get half of a percentage off.
You want people with pay on time.
You want no shut-offs.
Give them that senate.
You want to pour it here.
We don't want to raise it a pound time.
There's even a piece of why to let it fall down.
But the exclusion is if you use the drop-off.
What's the difference in the value of the party?
You don't have to let the check.
Yeah.
I'm going to get that.
We know that it happens.
We know that it's going to happen.
That's why we put the, you can't hold this responsible.
You've got 14 properties.
And you're not going to let us.
The scan keeps the error from happening.
Otherwise, you have humans.
We don't know if people have a 14 account.
So we're applying it as the best we can.
And that's why that's a good one.
The other thing is that we have a plan.
It's a plan.
You know.
You know, which life you would use.
They can for your act.
That's right.
The point is that if somebody goes through that, they have to enter the account number.
In that, we're at the work.
So if we didn't get the accuracy, but we're looking for the work.
There's not a line.
No one in the issue.
Because they're telling us that act, tell us specifically, which act.
It's what you have to think it is because the pause of money.
With that, it is time for the hands that that might be used to give me.
This is actually showing you which account that is, though, because whenever I fail,
I'm excited for it and for the pain that's not going to go.
All you do is you've been hearing your camera yourself, there is no terrifying evidence for anything like that.
I'm just going to keep back from your wrong account, I'm going to remind you somewhere.
So go somewhere.
That's correct.
But if it ends up in your being shut off because it was not credited to hear anything about it.
Because if you're mistaken, you know, again, what we're trying to avoid is the city being held wide away as we can get into the past.
And even when I'm trying to process whatever this came up, I have problems with the attention,
because I wanted to know what people could do to your health.
And that's when they came up with the idea of the pain online.
And I didn't say that there was an irony to pay online.
And then they don't care if you better go out and count on three pounds.
And it goes all back.
You know, you can see there's a care about those things that correct the counter problem.
Why is the difference?
It's just up.
And at the same time, it's like also trying to minimize these issues.
You can turn it like in the same time.
Well, I mean, for my perspective, not that big of a deal.
I mean, for any of you to tell us which one of the ones I've heard 50 or 30 of our leaders I have,
but they're not even a criminal.
It makes a whole lot more sense to put into tell us that.
And that's trying to figure it out.
And then you should set it for those certain businesses and have more than two, three, four counts.
And these go to them.
Not to the background on who has to run my payment to me,
because I'm not worthy to keep it off and I have a bill.
Well, again, if you have one again.
I don't know.
And I think about my house that's here.
Situation happened.
Well, I understand that, you know, one of our big problems is there's my more to care.
Multiple, multiple attacks.
And my family with a check.
My house, where is the real deal?
How are we supposed to figure that out?
Well, that's your standpoint to the people that have the issue.
Well, that's what we're talking about.
You don't have to deal with it.
I don't have to deal with it.
I don't deal with it.
You leave lots of important cases.
I don't have to deal with it.
The check.
Once they start to print those out,
they'll work out.
And it's a charge for those that they're not.
If you walk in, then just play your house.
Right now.
Then you don't get to talk about things you don't have.
I don't know.
I just think that situation happened.
And it should be applied directly.
That's not fair.
If that's what we're looking at.
I don't know.
For individuals, they're all individuals are in the charge.
Could we thank you so much by saying that this is happening in my yard?
Sure.
Could you make it separate if you set a business, have to pay that hard job for you?
So for example, if you have a board to do copies, you're down low-c.
So if you're down low-c, you're a business corporation,
if it doesn't operate, could you pay the only business,
if it doesn't work?
Or if you don't pay the mic, I have two different years.
I believe they don't even have one in mind.
One of my accounts, and so I didn't have the one to be at once.
I got to start with my penalty.
But it doesn't even count.
Which is fine with me.
Because I don't have to account much of a debt.
I think what you completely eliminate,
if I don't be on the penalty, have one.
No question.
If you only have one account, what?
Right.
If you're a business person.
That's a business person.
Yeah.
But if you're a business person, there's always, you can say,
When you're built, you're a business person.
You can pay that hard.
Well,
that's what we're trying to tell.
If you're paying on multiple accounts,
or you're built.
But it says,
It will not be accepted to pause unless you do get a drop off.
What?
Yeah.
I really want to get back with you on that,
because I don't remember that particular discussion.
That was early on in those conversations.
It's exactly what I said.
It shuts down the timing of everything.
It creates,
it creates a crisis created on a packet to do that $5 fee.
There's just a one.
So, our processes are, you change the one little thing,
and the amount of money will make the change.
So, our process is very detailed on the data shut up.
And we have to run on this one out of the box.
And if all these things occur,
which will be applying these fees,
which is going to take a packet,
and the packet is a process that takes time
and to apply it and to do it correctly.
And in that hour of time,
when you have this kind of time,
it's going to, you know,
and then you have one of those things.
On the whole day,
it will shut up,
but this is,
we get from a implicit balance.
There's just no way.
It shuts everything down.
So, if we don't implicit balance,
we can get it out of a certain time.
We can shut the people up.
And then they'll have time to get you out of their shut-off.
Because if we come up with lunch or whatever,
then we start to turn them on by the afternoon.
Otherwise, you're going to shut the process at night,
which has been causing over time situation.
And it will work.
It's really the only time you have this issue
to love the assumption of it.
I'm sorry, what?
We only time you really ever had the issues with this,
is on shut-off, right?
I'm sorry, what?
We only time.
But this is the point.
It's time to go.
Once upon a time, we would do shut-offs.
We have the same day, every week,
right now.
Just to think.
getting a good question.
So a lot of people, mostly,
or I didn't know this was there.
That would be fine enough,
and there's on the ground person for that,
so I don't have to rinse my clothes or as a mind,
because we're sort of responsible.
A lot of people don't know a lot of homes.
There are different names.
They want to be a landlord,
but they don't get a lot of them.
They don't get a lot of them.
And we don't know that.
We don't know that.
They don't get a lot of them.
Most of the residents, yes, yes.
There are a lot of people.
Some of them, like primarily,
we're trying to put this on.
Those are doing this at the window.
In really trying to prevent those individuals
from showing up window at multiple accounts.
They're creating the issue.
So that's where the five dollar fee is being applied.
Everyone else.
They don't think we're saying we can work with individuals at one account.
We can work with the individuals that are dropping off because if that's the entire procedure,
it will be timely.
But do you want to keep the window moving quickly and make sure that they're showing up
to the bills that they've got multiple accounts.
And that's the only place to find out if you want it.
So we're really trying to narrow that in and just solving that one problem.
Maybe you like likely to be asked by you.
Maybe you can order it to try to get some of the options
or you don't know about that.
We can put some.
I mean, we've publicized that as much as we can as many avenues.
You guys have other ways for us to publicize that.
That's one reason.
That's another reason why we should have done the drive there is because we got six of our options.
Now we have seven drive.
We're actually seven places for people to pay versus two.
Does it stay on the bill?
Yes.
We put it down.
It's everywhere.
We can pay down to put it.
It's basically, it's become an actually in one way or another.
Because it's a lot of people watching the reader come.
Right.
It helps.
It's not very hard about the bill.
Like they will take off.
So we're trying to look again at the report that you know.
And we're currently still going to share it with that bitter envelope to fees.
So we get those to those possible.
Because again, we want to try to balance your rights to that point.
And we want to move on.
We want to solve the problems.
We want to put it down.
Because it's a much more sophisticated portal to your point.
Josh.
We're going to make you do the count.
It also has the ability to take.
Hey, let's run the mobile, hey, hey, hey, I hope it's that one of the two that has people I want to talk about.
And when we roll that out, there's going to be a whole new campaign to the private option, where there's education, anything we can do to get people to drive it.
This will probably be another conversation that we've listed. Let's figure out what we can do to drive it out.
And that is all that you're talking about.
What are you going to do with the difference?
We're going to go back to China with our sorry.
Alan, Larry, I'm going to explain.
What are you going to do?
Okay.
Andrewson.